we-care.com 2014-12-24

# We-Care.com :: Privacy Policy

We-Care.com knows that you care about how information about you is handled. We value your trust and are committed to using private data respectfully and transparently.

We-Care.com allows nonprofits, schools, associations and other organizations that can receive contributions ("Causes") to receive donations when their supporters shop online at participating merchants ("Merchants"). We-Care.com is a wholly owned subsidiary of the Internet Marketing Group, Ltd. so when we say "we" or "our" or "us", we mean both We-Care.com and the Internet Marketing Group, Ltd. This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") describes the data collection, use and sharing policies we employ with respect to data collected at the We-Care.com web site (the "Site"), data collected via our We-Care software applications ("We-Care Software"), and data collected through our related end user services and non-web Internet applications such as the "Shop & Give Gadget" (collectively, the "Services"). The Services, including the We-Care Software are provided free of charge. For more information, please refer to our terms of services, accessible at www.we-care.com/TOS and our FAQs, accessible at www.we-care.com/About/FAQ. By using any of the We-Care.com Services, you are consenting to the use, collection and sharing of information collected from you as described below in this Privacy Policy.

### Registration and Personally Identifiable Information

We-Care.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information about you unless you choose to provide it to us, either by registering at our Site (which is completely optional) or by voluntarily contacting us and providing us with your email address or other personally identifiable information.

You do not have to register in order to view the content of our Site, to have a portion of your online purchases at our Merchants donated to your favorite Cause, or to download, install and use the We-Care Software. However, registering at our Site allows you to take advantage of certain enhanced features. For example, registered users may: (i) view their account and a record of their donations at any time they log into the Site to determine how much they have donated, (ii) set preferences, and (iii) receive emails that announce changes to our Services, new services we are offering, or special deals and programs. 

If you do decide to register, you may change the information we have on file for you at any time simply by logging into the Site and clicking on the "My Account" link at the top of the page. You may also decline to receive emails from us at the time of registration, or opt out of receiving them later by changing your preferences accessible via the "My Account Link" or by following the opt-out instructions included with each email. Please note that it may take up to ten (10) business days to process your request.

From time to time, we may provide you with the opportunity to participate in surveys. If you choose to participate, we may request certain personally identifiable and/or demographic information from you. Participation in such surveys is completely optional. You may also elect, at your discretion, to provide demographic information during the registration process (such as your age, income, geographic location, or gender).

We-Care.com uses your personally identifiable information to provide you with the Services and for the purposes described above, such as managing your account and preferences, tracking your donations, sending you email communications and responding to your questions or inquiries. If we haven't identified a particular purpose, you can generally assume that we will use your personally identifiable information for the purpose for which it was provided.

### Information We Collect and How We Use It

#### Server Logs

Server logs capture information that is typically not personally identifiable, such as the time and date of a Site visit, the browser and operating system being used, the IP address or domain name of the user's ISP, and the web URL a user linked from. This information is generally used to help us plan system enhancements when necessary and to provide content which is compatible with our users web browsing systems and in certain cases when your behavior has lead to a donation, in order to attribute the value of your donation-generating behavior to your selected Cause account. Because We-Care.com does keep a log of your IP address as well as certain purchase, search or advertising behaviors for the purposes of generating or allocating donation revenue to your chosen cause there is a possibility that some combination of search, social media or site visitation behavior could alone or in combination reveal personally identifiable information about you. We-Care.com does not engage in the mining of log data with the express intent of determining your identity or generating personally identifiable information. When you have provided us with registration information, server logs may be used to provide you with reporting information as to your current and past donation behaviors and activities.

Cookies, Local Shared Objects on Our Site and Digital Finger printing Cookies

We-Care.com uses cookies to provide you with a more customized experience and ensure that the donations arising from your shopping and other activities online are credited to the intended organizations.

A cookie, or Local Shared Object (Flash Cookie) is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information, but do contain a unique user ID and may contain IDs for the Causes you have selected to support through the Site. If you choose to register, the user ID is linked to your account, allowing you to track your donations.

Depending on participating merchant policies, tracking cookies are set when you visit our site, when you visit a merchant site, or when you click on the link provided by the We-Care Software.

We set cookies to store your user name (if provided), your favorite Cause and other information so you don't have to enter this information every time you visit our Site. We also use cookies for non-registered users to track them based on an anonymous user ID. Cookies also enable us to track users sessions on the Site, such as features that you use, actions that you take, and the information you access. We use this information to target the interests of our users and enhance their experience on the Site. Similarly, we use this information in statistical and aggregate formats to assess the effectiveness of our Site and to better understand your priorities and interests.

We also employ a technology called clear web beacons (also known as clear pixels and clear gifs) placed in the pages of our Site to help us gather additional information about which parts of the Site receive the most visits and other user traffic patterns. Web beacons do not typically contain or collect personally identifiable information, but do contain a unique user ID that tracks online movements. We use web beacons to help us learn how users are using the Services, which in turn helps us operate and improve those Services. We also use web beacons so that we can understand your browsing behavior and provide Merchants and other third parties with information regarding user interactions with them, such as when and how often their coupons and offers are displayed.

We may also use cookies and web beacons in our email campaigns so we can determine which emails have been opened by our users. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

If you have registered at the Site, cookies or Web beacons may contain your user ID information which we can then match with other information collected from you in order to provide you with the additional functionality available only to registered users.

You can set your browser to reject most cookies by following the browser help file directions. However, if your browser is set to reject cookies or you delete cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our Site or other websites. You can also delete cookies already set on your computer by following the browser help file directions.

In order to facilitate tracking and properly maximize the value your shopping, searching and ad-viewing behavior and deliver proper share of the dollar value you are generating for your cause the We-Care Software may make adjustments to your browsers default Do-Not-Track settings to allow our Software to communicate with our tracking servers and the servers of our partners. We will place information about your DNT settings in the Software's administrative screens whenever possible.

The We-Care Software collects and transmits back to our servers certain information that is not personally identifiable such as which Internet browser you are using, which version of our software you downloaded, your software application preferences and whether you have certain features enabled or disabled.

In addition, the We-Care Software transmits information to us to let us know when you visit the website of a Merchant and when you make a purchase from that Merchant to help us ensure the Cause that you have chosen receives the applicable donation for your purchase.

We-Care Software may collect and transmit to We-Care.com information about the web sites you visit and your activities on those web sites, which may include the purchases you make (or decide to abandon), searches you perform, ads you see or click through, videos you watch, and/or non-personally identifiable, data you submit into web forms on web sites. Generally, all of this information is collected and transmitted on an anonymous basis, using an anonymous user ID, and is not associated with your name, email address or other personally identifiable information. However, you should be aware that if you submit personally identifiable information into web forms, this information may be transmitted back to We-Care.com. However, we will not use such personally identifiable information for marketing purposes nor intentionally associate it with non personally identifiable information about you.

In addition, third-party cookies may be set by partners based on your search or commerce behavior for the purpose of serving you more relevant messages and advertising. Resulting Online Behavioral Advertising may appear within the We-Care Software, on the We-Care.com Site and on other sites. Partner data payments are donated to your chosen cause on a pro-rata basis in keeping with We-Care policies, which means that the value of your anonymous browsing and searching behavior will help your selected cause.

You should also be aware that, notwithstanding anything to the contrary contained in this Privacy Policy, it is possible that the We-Care Software will collect and transmit personally identifiable information, including potentially sensitive data, due to inconsistencies in the way web sites identify data fields. While We-Care.com does not intend to collect this kind of personally identifiable information, there will likely be instances when this information will be inadvertently collected or transmitted. However, we will never knowingly use inadvertently collected personally identifiable information for marketing purposes. 

In order to remove OBA (Online Behavioral Advertising) third party cookes from your browser, visit the NAI website at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/> or the Digital Advertising Alliance website at: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

#### Other uses:

In addition to the uses identified above, We-Care.com uses non personally identifiable information collected from users by the We-Care.com Software and other Services in the following ways:

  * To maintain, operate and provide the Services,
  * To improve the We-Care Software and other Services by determining which features are most often utilized by our users,
  * To help us understand how often certain Merchants are visited and/or appear in search results,
  * To help us ensure that applicable Causes receive the portion of your online purchases that they are entitled to,
  * To help us target advertisements and provide you with enhancements to your web browsing experience that may be of interest to you,
  * To help us create and determine the effectiveness of certain marketing campaigns and strategies, including email campaigns, 
  * To determine how many of our users select a particular Cause for Merchant donations or follow a particular Cause on a social media web site,
  * To perform market research and prepare reports and analysis which may be shared in aggregate form with third parties.

### How Do We Share the Information We Collect

We-care.com does not sell, distribute or disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent except in the limited circumstances expressly identified below (such as when legally required). We may share your personally identifiable information with Causes and our business associates if you have registered and indicated to us during registration that we are permitted to do so. If you indicate your assent but then change your mind, you may change your election at any time by logging into the Site or We-Care Software and changing your settings. However, you understand that we cannot retrieve your information from third parties that we have already received it. In addition, we may share your personally identifiable information with subcontractors, vendors and other businesses that we employ to perform functions on our behalf. For example, we may employ third parties to send email campaigns, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, or provide customer service. These entities have access to your information only for the purposes of performing the functions for which we have engaged them. If such entities have access to your personally identifiable information, their agreements with us require them to keep your information confidential. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information to comply with legal requirements or process, or where necessary to prevent or investigate fraud, to protect the safety of an individual, or to permit us to exercise our legal rights or enforce the terms of our Software License, Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy.

Lastly, if We-Care.com is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, or in the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to disclose, transfer and/or assign the information we have collected as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

With respect to non personally identifiable information collected about you in connection with your use of the Services, We-Care.com may sell, rent, disclose or otherwise share with third parties all such information. Please note that any time we share such information, it is not associated with your name, email or other personally identifiable information. Typically, it is disclosed in the form of aggregate statistics.

### Third Parties

This Privacy Policy applies only to information gathered by We-Care.com.

Some of our business associates (e.g., advertisers, affiliate networks, and analytics services) also serve cookies, web beacons and similar technologies through our Services. All data collected by such business associates using these tracking technologies is anonymous and is not linked to your personally identifiable information. This data may be used to determine site usage, target advertisements, analyze whether advertising resulted in sales, clicks, or other activity and for other purposes. These business partners include but are not limited to Google, Linkshare, Commission Junction, PepperJam, Appnexus, TheTradeDesk, CPX, Yahoo, Gigya, Impact Radius, and Didit. To learn more about how these companies use such data, please visit and check their respective privacy policies. 

When you visit one of our Merchants or Causes, or click through any link from our Site, you are leaving our Site. These third parties may use cookies and tracking technologies on their site for purposes that include identifying you as a user from We-Care.com in order to pay the commission on your purchase. (These commissions are the source of the donations we make on your behalf.) Many Merchants also use a third-party "affiliate network" to do this on their behalf. Please note that any information you provide to them or that is collected about you while visiting their websites is governed by their respective privacy policies.

The Services also contain links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us. Of course, we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such websites.

### Children

The Site and We-Care Software is not directed at children under the age of 13 and does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that the Site has collected the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us at the number or address listed below and we will use our best efforts to remove the information from our records.

### Storage

We may store your information for as long as need for the purposes indicated in this privacy policy, and that may be indefinitely. We store such information in the United States, typically within a cloud server infrastructure provided by Amazon.com, or a similar third party provider.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we use commercially reasonable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security or be responsible for any damage that results from a breach in security. If you have any questions about security on the Site, please contact us at the number or address listed below.

### Changes

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we do make modifications, we will post them on our Site, so please visit the Site and review the Privacy Policy frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we may also attempt to notify you by email (if you have registered to receive email from us) or by means of a notice on our homepage.

### Privacy Questions

If you have questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy or wish to correct, change, or verify any personal information we have about you, please [contact us](http://www.we-care.com/About/ContactUs?subject=Privacy+Policy).

**We-Care.com**  
Attn: Privacy Department  
108 West 39th Street Suite 1000  
New York, NY 10018  
800.768.1399 

_Updated: August 26, 2013_
